<resources>
    <string name="app_name">IEEE DS</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="industry_applications_society">Industry Applications Society</string>
    <string name="industry_applications_society_desc">The Industry Applications Society, as a transnational organization, is interested in advancement of the theory and practice of electrical and electronic engineering in the development, design, manufacture and application of electrical systems, apparatus, devices and controls to the processes and equipment of industry and commerce; promotion of safe, reliable and economic installations; industry leadership in energy conservation and environmental, health, and safety issues; creation of voluntary engineering standards and recommended practices; and the professional development of its membership.</string>
    <string name="power_and_energy_society">Power and Energy Society</string>
    <string name="power_and_energy_society_desc">The Power and Energy Society (PES) provides the world\'s largest forum for sharing the latest in technological developments in the electric power industry, for developing standards that guide the development and construction of equipment and systems, and for educating members of the industry and the general public. Members of the Power and Energy Society are leaders in this field, and they — and their employers — derive substantial benefits from involvement with this unique and outstanding association.</string>
    <string name="circuits_and_systems_society">Circuits and Systems Society</string>
    <string name="circuits_and_systems_society_desc">The IEEE Circuits and Systems Society is the leading organization that promotes the advancement of the theory, analysis, design, tools, and implementation of circuits and systems. The field spans their theoretical foundations, applications, and architectures, as well as circuits and systems implementation of algorithms for signal and information processing.</string>
    <string name="computer_society">Computer Society</string>
    <string name="computer_society_desc">The IEEE Computer Society is the world\'s leading membership organization dedicated to computer science and technology. Serving more than 60,000 members, the IEEE Computer Society is the trusted information, networking, and career-development source for a global community of technology leaders that includes researchers, educators, software engineers, IT professionals, employers, and students.</string>
    <string name="communications_society">Communications Society</string>
    <string name="communications_society_desc">The IEEE Communications Society promotes the advancement of science, technology and applications in communications and related disciplines. It fosters presentation and exchange of information among its members and the technical community throughout the world. The Society maintains the highest standard of professionalism and technical competency.</string>
    <string name="technology_and_engineering_management_society">Technology and Engineering Management Society</string>
    <string name="technology_and_engineering_management_society_desc">The Field of Interest of the TEMS encompasses the management sciences and practices required for defining, implementing, and managing engineering and technology. Specific topics of interest include, but are not limited to: technology policy development, assessment, and transfer; research; product design and development; manufacturing operations; innovation and entrepreneurship; program and project management; strategy; education and training; organizational development and human behaviour; transitioning to management; and the socioeconomic impact of engineering and technology management.</string>
    <string name="instrumentation_and_measurement_society">Instrumentation and Measurement Society</string>
    <string name="instrumentation_and_measurement_society_desc">The IEEE Instrumentation and Measurement Society is dedicated to the development and use of electrical and electronic instruments and equipment to measure, monitor and/or record physical phenomena. The fields of interest include metrology, analog and digital electronic instruments, systems and standards for measuring and recording electrical quantities (in both frequency and time domains), instrumentation and transducers for measurement of non-electrical variables, calibration and uncertainty, instruments with automated control and analysis functions, safety instrumentation, and new technology applications.</string>
    <string name="engineering_in_medicine_and_biology_society">Engineering in Medicine and Biology Society</string>
    <string name="engineering_in_medicine_and_biology_society_desc">The IEEE Engineering in Medicine and Biology Society benefits both humanity and its members by advancing medicine, biology, healthcare and well-being through the application of engineering and data sciences and technology, and promoting the profession of biomedical engineering, fostering professional development and recognizing excellence.</string>
    <string name="power_electronics_society">Power Electronics Society</string>
    <string name="power_electronics_society_desc">The Power Electronics Society is one of the fastest growing technical societies of the Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers (IEEE). For over 20 years, PELS has facilitated and guided the development and innovation in power electronics technology. This technology encompasses the effective use of electronic components, the application of circuit theory and design techniques, and the development of analytical tools toward efficient conversion, control and condition of electric power. Our members include preeminent researchers, practitioners, and distinguished award winners. IEEE PELS Publishes the IEEE Transactions on Power Electronics, a top referenced journal among all IEEE publications.</string>
    <string name="industrial_electronics_society">Industrial Electronics Society</string>
    <string name="industrial_electronics_society_desc">The Industrial Electronics Society through its members encompasses a diverse range of technical activities devoted to the application of electronics and electrical sciences for the enhancement of industrial and manufacturing processes. These technical activities address the latest developments in intelligent and computer control systems, robotics, factory communications and automation, flexible manufacturing, data acquisition and signal processing, vision systems, and power electronics. The Society continually updates its program of technical activities to meet the needs of modern industry.</string>
    <string name="electron_devices_society">Electron Devices Society</string>
    <string name="electron_devices_society_desc">The IEEE Electron Devices Society (EDS) is one of the technical societies and councils that you can join as an IEEE member. EDS began in 1952 as a committee of the Institute of Radio Engineers (IRE). With the merger in 1963 of the IRE and the American Institute of Radio Engineers, EDS became a technical group under the newly formed IEEE. In 1976, EDS became a society of IEEE. To respond to the more complex society structure and increased business activities, the Society established an Executive Office in 1990.</string>
    <string name="microwave_theory_and_techniques_society">Microwave Theory and Techniques Society</string>
    <string name="microwave_theory_and_techniques_society_desc">The IEEE Microwave Theory and Techniques Society (MTT-S) is a transnational society with more than 10,500 members and 190 chapters worldwide. Our society promotes the advancement of microwave theory and its applications, including RF, microwave, millimetre-wave, and terahertz technologies. As we enter into an exciting future, our mission is to continue to understand and influence microwave technology and to provide a forum for all microwave engineers. The MTT-S will continue to be the global focus for the promotion of the RF and microwave engineering profession, by advancing and distributing knowledge and supporting professional development.</string>
    <string name="computational_intelligence_society">Computational Intelligence Society</string>
    <string name="computational_intelligence_society_desc">The Field of Interest of the Society shall be the theory, design, application, and development of biologically and linguistically motivated computational paradigms emphasizing neural networks, connectionist systems, genetic algorithms, evolutionary programming, fuzzy systems, and hybrid intelligent systems in which these paradigms are contained.</string>
    <string name="geoscience_and_remote_sensing_society">Geoscience and Remote Sensing Society</string>
    <string name="geoscience_and_remote_sensing_society_desc">The fields of interest of the Society are the theory, concepts, and techniques of science and engineering as they apply to the remote sensing of the earth, oceans, atmosphere, and space, as well as the processing, interpretation and dissemination of this information.</string>
    <string name="solid_state_circuits_society">Solid-State Circuits Society</string>
    <string name="solid_state_circuits_society_desc">With over 9,000 members around the world, the IEEE Solid-State Circuits Society focuses on fabricated integrated circuit designs in contrast to simulated circuits and analysed models for all applications using relevant materials and interconnections. The Society produces the Journal of Solid-State Circuits (JSSC), the most downloaded technical journal in IEEE Xplore, and sponsors the International Solid-State Circuits Conference (ISSCC), the world\'s premier circuits realization conference.</string>
    <string name="education_society">Education Society</string>
    <string name="education_society_desc">The IEEE Education Society is an international organization that promotes, advances, and disseminates state-of-the-art scientific information and resources related to the Society’s field of interest and provides professional development opportunities for academic and industry professionals.</string>
    <string name="signal_processing_society">Signal Processing Society</string>
    <string name="signal_processing_society_desc">The IEEE\'s first society, the Signal Processing Society is the world’s premier professional society for signal processing scientists and professionals since 1948. Signal processing is the enabling technology for the generation, transformation, and interpretation of information. SPS serves its members through high quality publications, conferences, technical and educational activities, and leadership opportunities. Its goal is to keep members abreast of the latest information and to serve the public at large.</string>
    <string name="women_in_engineering_affinity_group">Women In Engineering Affinity Group</string>
    <string name="women_in_engineering_affinity_group_desc">IEEE WIE is one of the world’s leaders in changing the face of engineering. Our network connects over 24,000 members in over 100 countries to professional women around the world. IEEE WIE membership gives you access to a global network that advances professional women in technology at all points in their life and career. IEEE WIE members make lifelong friendships, acquire influential mentors and make a difference for the benefit of humanity.</string>
    <string name="young_professionals_affinity_group">Young Professionals Affinity Group</string>
    <string name="young_professionals_affinity_group_desc">IEEE Young Professionals is the group of IEEE members and volunteers who have graduated from their first professional degree within the past 15 years. It is an international community, whose members are interested in elevating their professional image, expanding their global network, connecting with peers locally and giving back to their community. Since it encompasses all members from recent university graduates to experienced professionals and entrepreneurs, the group is highly diverse in what it has to offer.</string>
    <string name="ieee_brain">IEEE Brain</string>
    <string name="ieee_brain_desc">The mission of IEEE Brain is to facilitate cross-disciplinary collaboration and coordination to advance research, standardization and development of technologies in neuroscience to help improve the human condition.</string>
    <string name="control_systems_society">Control Systems Society</string>
    <string name="control_systems_society_desc">The Society is dedicated to the advancement of research, development, and practice in automation and control systems. It has broad technical interests in dynamical systems and control that include modelling, adaptation, estimation, optimization, feedback and software/hardware tools. Application areas include aerospace, automotive, biosystems, communication networks, finance and markets, homes and buildings, manufacturing and process industries, and micro/nano-systems. The Society publishes its research in its highly ranked journals and technical conferences.</string>
</resources>
